Guide to the Wilfrid S. Sellars Papers, 1899-1990 ASP.1991.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Professional Activities, 1935-1989; IV.
  - Correspondence, 1935-1989; 2.
    - Individuals
      - Thomson, Judith, 1979 (Box 162, Folder 16)
      - Turnball, Robert, 1950-1984 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - Vlastos, Gregory, 1950-1974 (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - Weiss, Paul, 1952-1981 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Wells, Rulon, 1949-1972 (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Williams, Donald, 1949-1963 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence by Topic
      - Copy requests, 1948-1983 (Box 163, Folder 6-10)
      - Copy requests, 1948-1981 (Box 164, Folder 1-3)
      - Evaluations of philosophy departments, 1967-1979 (Box 164, Folder 4)
      - Fellowships, 1937-1981 (Box 164, Folder 5)
      - Job offers, 1966-1974 (Box 164, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1948-1984 (Box 164, Folder 7-9)
      - Offprints with cover letters, 1951-1983 (Box 165, Folder 1-3)
      - Philosophical debates, 1960-1982 (Box 165, Folder 4-7)
      - Philosophical debates, 1951-1985 (Box 166, Folder 1-4)
      - Publishers/editors, 1948-1987 (Box 166, Folder 5-7)
      - Publishers/editors, 1950-1987 (Box 167, Folder 1-8)
      - Requests for recommendations, 1952-1985 (Box 167, Folder 9-10)
      - Requests for recommendations, 1951-1988 (Box 168, Folder 1-5)
      - Reviews and critiques, 1951-1983 (Box 168, Folder 6-8)
      - Roy Wood Sellars subject file, 1966-1985 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Speaking engagements, 1950-1985 (Box 169, Folder 1-6)
      - Speaking engagements, 1955-1983 (Box 170, Folder 1-3)
      - Visiting professorships, 1949-1976 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Editorship of Philosophical Studies, 1957-1989; 3.
    These files chronicle Sellars establishment and editorship of the journal Philosophical Studies from 1951-1989. These files also document the creation of a related book series, Philosophical Studies Series in Philosophy. Most of the files pertain to the journal and consist of correspondence. Largely composed of cover letters, this correspondence originates from philosophers who are submitting their manuscripts for publication. The cover letters are supplemented by a limited amount of manuscripts, as well as letters of acceptance, rejection notices, or evaluations of the manuscripts. The correspondence with publishers illuminates the process of selecting and arranging published articles, as well as granting permission to reproduce articles. In addition to correspondence the subseries contain a log book of manuscripts as well as referee reports. These reports are especially important, since they provide researchers with succinct evaluations of a philosopher's argument. The files relating to the journal phase out in 1974, when Sellars decided to resign as editor and focus on the development of the book series. The book series correspondence is similar to the article submission correspondence and highlights the types of manuscripts submitted for publication.
    - Journal
      - Contract, 1971 (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence on article submissions, 1957-1962 (Box 170, Folder 6-9)
      - Correspondence on article submissions, 1963-1967 (Box 171, Folder 1-8)
      - Correspondence on article submissions, 1968-1972 (Box 172, Folder 1-8)
      - Correspondence on article submissions, 1972-1974 (Box 173, Folder 1-7)
      - Correspondence on article submissions, 1973-1974 (Box 174, Folder 1-5)
      - Correspondence of editorial board, 1971-1974 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence with Minnesota Press, 1949-1974 (Box 174, Folder 7-9)
      - Correspondence with Reidel, 1970-1976 (Box 175, Folder 1-4)
      - Log book, 1949-1959 (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Referee reports, 1965-1975 (Box 175, Folder 6-7)
    - Book Series
      - Contracts, 1973-1978 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1989 (Box 176, Folder 1-4)
  - Professional Societies, 1939-1987; 4.
    These files document Sellars's activity within various professional associations, committees, foundations, and societies. The files are arranged alphabetically by organization title. He was particularly involved with the American Philosophical Association and these files document his participation in several committees. Extensive files exist for the Federation Internationale Des Societes De Philosophie, which reveal Sellars's interest in the international philosophical community. This section also contains files related to Sellars's service on the editorial board of The Monist. Mostly consisting of correspondence, these files document the process of developing the quarterly issues of the journal. The National Science Foundation files document Sellars's activity as a consultant to the History and Philosophy of Science division, as well as his own grant proposals.
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1971-1987 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1952-1973 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - American Catholic Philosophical Association, 1971-1974 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1964, 1971 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - American Philosophical Association
      - Board of officers, 1969-1970 (Box 176, Folder 9)
      - Committee on International Cooperation, 1968-1973 (Box 176, Folder 10)
      - General, 1964-1972 (Box 176, Folder 11)
      - General, 1974-1981 (Box 177, Folder 1-2)
      - Executive Committee, 1967-1983 (Box 177, Folder 3-7)
      - Nominating Committee, 1971 (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Program Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - American Philosophical Quarterly, 1962-1979 (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Association of Philosophy Journal Editors, 1971-1977 (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - Center for Advanced Study in the Behavior Sciences, 1975-1978 (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - Council for Philosophical Studies
      - General, 1964-1972 (Box 178, Folder 6-7)
      - Visiting philosopher program, 1968 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Federation Internationale Des Societes De Philosophie, 1965-1971 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Federation Internationale Des Societes De Philosophie, 1972-1983 (Box 179, Folder 1-6)
    - Humanist Society, 1939-1942 (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - Hume Society, 1978-1983 (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - Institute of Intercultural Research, 1973-1974 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Leibniz Society, 1978-1983 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Metaphysical Society of America, 1971-1985 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Mind Association, 1965-1984 (Box 180, Folder 4-5)
    - Miscellaneous Societies, 1952-1984 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Monist,Correspondence, 1961-1982 (Box 180, Folder 7-12)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities1968-1978 (Box 181, Folder 1-2)
    - National Science Foundation
      - Consulting, 1962-1974 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Research project, 1963-1978 (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Rhodes Scholarship Trust, 1953-1958 (Box 181, Folder 5-6)
    - Philosophy of Science Association
      - General, 1970-1985 (Box 181, Folder 7-8)
      - Biennial meeting, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1969, 1972 (Box 182, Folder 2)
- Library, V.
  This series is composed of 792 annotated books, 144 annotated reprints and off-prints, about 180 annotated journal volumes, which were amassed by Wilfrid Sellars from the 1930s through the 1980s. This series also contains a set of off-prints and books written and retained by Sellars himself. The books and offprints are arranged alphabetically by author and title, while the journals are arranged by journal title and then chronologically by issue. The library contains material spanning the whole of Sellars' career. The topics covered reflect Sellars' professional concerns and therefore contain works on a wide variety of philosophical topics, but emphasize works on logic, epistemology, ontology, scientific realism, philosophy of science, ancient Greek philosophy, and the history of philosophy. Many of these works contain either annotations or dedications. The annotations include notes in the margins of the documents, underlining, and logical notations. The degree and kind of annotation vary greatly; some items are heavily underlined, annotated, and logically notated. Others have only short sections that are heavily marked, or are lightly marked throughout.
  A large portion of the library was deaccessioned; the deaccessioned materials include books, journals, and reprints that were not philosophical in nature and lacked any unique markings such as annotations or dedications. These items covered a broad spectrum of Sellars' personal interests and ranged from sports to crosswords, nature, cooking, politics, biographies, history, religion, art, and works of fiction. There is a comprehensive list of all the books initially contained in Sellars's library available for researchers upon request. There is also a list of journal titles found in the Sellars's library.
  - Annotated Books, dates; 1.
    This subseries consists of 792 books which have information in the form of annotations, dedications to Sellars, or inclusions. The books are arranged alphabetically by author, editor, or occasionally by translator. The annotations take the form of notes in the margins of the documents, underlining, and logical notations and derivations. The degree and kind of annotation vary greatly; some books are heavily underlined, annotated, and logically notated. Others have only short sections that are heavily marked, or are lightly marked throughout. There are dedications to Sellars from family members or other philosophers, and there are dedications from Wilfrid to his father. There are also books that contained inclusions. These inclusions can consist of fairly extended written commentary. They are sometimes commentary on the book in which they were found, and sometimes on other philosophical or personal topics.
    In addition there are a few books that may not be marked, but are on topics that were of particular interest to Sellars. These books contained many slips of paper which acted as book markers. For example, his editions of Kant are included although they are not marked, because they contain hundreds of book markers and show considerable signs of use. In general, the books in this series are books on philosophical topics. They include editions of the works of the central figures in European philosophy such as Hume, Locke, Descartes, Kant, and Russell. Many of these are student editions that he seems to have used during his days at Oxford and Harvard. They are often extensively annotated with both marginal notes and underlining.
    A list of annotated books is available.
    - Bergmann, Gustav. Logic and Reality. University of Wisconsin Press, 1964 (Box 182, Item 1)
    - Cassirer, H.W. Kant's First Critique, An Appraisal of the Permanent Significance of Kant's Critique of Pure Reason. George Allen & Unwin Ltd. London, England, 1954 (Box 182, Item 2)
    - Cherniss, Harold. Aristotle's Criticism of Plato and the Academy, Volume I. The Johns Hopkins Press, 1944 (Box 182, Item 3)
    - Davis, J.W. et al. Philosophical Logic. D. Reidel Publishing Company, 1969 (Box 182, Item 4)
    - Elwes, R.H.M. The Chief Works of Benedict de Spinoza, translated from the Latin, with an introduction (volumes I and II bound together). Dover Publications Inc., 1951 (Box 182, Item 5)
    - Feigl, Herbert et al. Minnesota Studies in the Philosophy of Science, Volume I: The Foundations of Science and the Concepts of Psychology and Psychoanalysis. University of Minnesota Press, 1956 (Box 182, Item 6)
    - Feigl, Herbert et al. Minnesota Studies in the Philosophy of Science, Volume II: Concepts, Theories, and the Mind-Body Problem. University of Minnesota Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 7)
    - Feigl, Herbert et al. Minnesota Studies in the Philosophy of Science, Volume III: Scientific Explanation, Space, and Time. University of Minnesota Press, 1962 (Box 182, Item 8)
    - Gilson, Etienne. Being and Some Philosophers. Pontifical Institute of Mediaeval Studies, Mediaeval Studies of Toronto, Inc., 1949 (Box 182, Item 9)
    - Hall, Everett W. What is Value? An Essay in Philosophical Analysis. Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd., 1952 (Box 182, Item 10)
    - Kazemier, B.H. et al. Logic and Language: Studies Dedicated to Professor Rudolf Carnap on the Occasion of his Seventieth Birthday. D. Reidel Publishing Company, 1962 (Box 182, Item 11)
    - Keynes, John Maynard. The General Theory of Employment Interest and Money. Macmillan and Co., Limited, 1936 (Box 182, Item 12)
    - Moore, George Edward. Commonplace Book, 1919-1953. George Allen & Unwin Ltd., 1962 (Box 182, Item 13)
    - Nagel, Ernest. Logic Without Metaphysics, and Other Essays in the Philosophy of Science. The Free Press, 1956 (Box 182, Item 14)
    - Nagel, Ernest. The Structure of Science: Problems in the Logic of Scientific Explanation. Harcourt, Brace & World, Inc., 1961 (Box 182, Item 15)
    - Popper, Karl R. The Logic of Scientific Discovery. Hutchinson & Co. (Publishers) Ltd., of London, 1959, third impression 1962 (Box 182, Item 16)
    - Prior, Arthur N. Logic and the Basis of Ethics. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1949 (Box 182, Item 17)
    - Van Orman Quine, Willard. Set Theory and Its Logic. The Belknap Press of Harvard University Press, 1963 (Box 182, Item 18)
    - Ross, David, Sir. Plato's Theory of Ideas. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1951 (Box 182, Item 19)
    - Saw, Ruth Lydia. The Vindication of Metaphysics: A Study in the Philosophy of Spinoza. Macmillan and Co., Ltd., 1951 (Box 182, Item 20)
    - Alighieri, Dante. The Divine Comedy. The Modern Library, Inc., 1932 (Box 182, Item 21)
    - Eaton, Ralph M. General Logic: An Introductory Survey. Charles Scribner's Sons, 1931 (Box 182, Item 22)
    - Hoenen, Peter, S.J. Reality and Judgment according to St. Thomas. Henry Regnery Company, 1952 (Box 182, Item 23)
    - Joseph, H.W.B. Lectures on the Philosophy of Leibniz. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1949 (Box 182, Item 24)
    - Lewis, Clarence Irving. An Analysis of Knowledge and Valuation. The Open Court Publishing Company, 1946 (Box 182, Item 25)
    - Lewis, Clarence Irving. Mind and the World-Order: Outline of a Theory of Knowledge. Charles Scribner's Sons, 1929 (Box 182, Item 26)
    - Oates, Whitney J. The Stoic and Epicurean Philosophers: The complete extant writings of Epicurus, Epictetus, Lucretius, Marcus Aurelius. Random House, Inc., 1940 (Box 182, Item 27)
    - Paton, H.J. Kant's Metaphysic of Experience: A Commentary on the First Half of the Kritik Der Reinen Vernunft. George Allen & Unwin Ltd, 1936 (Box 182, Item 28)
    - Wilson, John Cook. Statement and Interference, with other philosophical papers, Vol.1. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1926 (Box 182, Item 29)
    - Wilson, John Cook. Statement and Interference, with other philosophical papers, Vol.2. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1926 (Box 182, Item 30)
    - Wittgenstein, Ludwig. Philosophische Untersuchungen/Philosophical Investigations (German/English translation). Basil Blackwell, 1953 (Box 182, Item 31)
    - Vleeschauwer, H.J. de. La Deduction Transcendentale dans L'oeuvre de Kant. Tome Premier, La Deduction Transcendentale avant la Critique de la Raison Pure. Librairie Ancienne Honore Champion, 1934 (Box 182, Item 32)
    - Lakatos, I. Proofs and Refutations, Offprint from The British Journal for the Philosophy of Science, Vol. XIV, Nos. 53-56. Thomas Nelson & Sons Ltd, 1963, 1964 (Box 182, Item 33)
    - Bernard, J.H. Kant's Critique of Judgement. Macmillan and Co., Limited, 1931 (Box 182, Item 34)
    - Broad, C.D. The Mind and its Place in Nature. Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner, & Co., Ltd., 1929 (Box 182, Item 35)
    - Church, Ralph W. Hume's Theory of the Understanding. George Allen & Unwin Ltd., 1935 (Box 182, Item 36)
    - Dewey, John. How We Think: A Restatement of the Relation of Reflective Thinking to the Educative Process. D.C. Heath and Company, 1933 (Box 182, Item 37)
    - Jessop, T.E. Berkeley Philosophical Writings. University of Texas Press, 1953 (Box 182, Item 38)
    - Kneale, William and Martha Kneale. The Development of Logic. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1962 (Box 182, Item 39)
    - Lewis, Clarence Irving and Cooper Harold Langford. Symbolic Logic. The Century Co., 1932 (Box 182, Item 40)
    - Ross, W.D. Aristotle. Methuen & Co. Ltd., 1930 (Box 182, Item 41)
    - Selby-Bigge, L.A. Hume's Treatise of Human Nature. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1896 (Box 182, Item 42)
    - Sellars, Wilfrid and John Hospers. Readings in Ethical Theory. Appleton-Century-Crofts, Inc., 1952 (Box 182, Item 43)
    - Weldon, T.D. Introduction to Kant's Critique of Pure Reason. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1945 (Box 182, Item 44)
    - Weldon, T.D. Kant's Critique of Pure Reason. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1958 (Box 182, Item 45)
    - Wiener, Philip P. Leibniz Selections. Charles Scribner's Sons, 1951 (Box 182, Item 46)
    - Chase, D.P. The Nicomachean Ethics of Aristotle. J.M. Dent & Sons, 1911 (Box 182, Item 47)
    - Cornford, Francis MacDonald. Plato and Parmenides: Parmenides' Way of Truth and Plato's Parmenides translated and with a running Commentary. Routledge & Kegan Paul Ltd, 1939 (Box 182, Item 48)
    - Cornford, Francis MacDonald. The Republic of Plato translated with introduction and notes. Oxford University Press, 1945 (Box 182, Item 49)
    - Ewing, A.C. Idealism: A Critical Survey. Methuen & Co. Ltd., 1934 (Box 182, Item 50)
    - Foster, M.B. The Political Philosophies of Plato and Hegel. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1935 (Box 182, Item 51)
    - Gewirth, Alan. Marsilius of Padua: The Defender of Peace, Volume II: The Defensor pacis, translated with an introduction. Columbia University Press, 1956 (Box 182, Item 52)
    - Green, Thomas Hill. Prolegomena to Ethics. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1906 (Box 182, Item 53)
    - McKeon, Richard. The Basic Works of Aristotle edited and with an introduction. Random House, Inc., 1941 (Box 182, Item 54)
    - Moore, G.E. Philosophical Studies. Kegan, Paul, Trench, Trubner, & Co., Ltd., 1922 (Box 182, Item 55)
    - Ramsey, Frank Plumpton. The Foundations of Mathematics and other Logical Essays. Kegan, Paul, Trench, Trubner, & Co., Ltd., 1931 (Box 182, Item 56)
    - Rome, Beatrice K. The Philosophy of Malebranche: A Study of his Integration of Faith, Reason, and Experimental Observation. Henry Regnery Company, 1963 (Box 182, Item 57)
    - Schilpp, Paul Arthur. The Philosophy of G.E. Moore. Northwestern University, 1942 (Box 182, Item 58)
    - Smith, J.A. and W.D. Ross. The Works of Aristotle Translated into English. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, 1908 (Box 182, Item 59)
    - Wright, Georg Henrik von. A Treatise on Induction and Probability. Routledge and Kegan Paul, 1951 (Box 182, Item 60)
    - Ayer, Alfred J. Language, Truth, and Logic. Victor Gollancz Ltd., 1936 (Box 182, Item 61)
    - Bradley, F.H. Appearance and Reality: A Metaphysical Essay. Swan Sonnenschein & Co., Lim., 1902 (Box 182, Item 62)
    - Broad, C.D. Scientific Thought. Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co., Ltd., 1927 (Box 182, Item 63)
    - Ewing, A.C. Kant's Treatment of Casuality. Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co., Ltd., 1924 (Box 182, Item 64)
    - Nicod, Jean. Foundations of Geometry & Induction. Kegan Paul, Trench, Trubner & Co., Ltd., 1930 (Box 182, Item 65)
    - Pitcher, George. The Philosophy of Wittgenstein. Prentice-Hall, Inc., 1964 (Box 182, Item 66)
    - Prichard, H.A. Knowlegde and Perception: Essays and Lectures. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1950 (Box 182, Item 67)
    - Sellars, Roy Wood. The Philosophy of Physical Realism. The Macmillan Company, 1932 (Box 182, Item 68)
    - Wittgenstein, Ludwig. Bemerkungen uber die Grundlagen der Mathematik/Remarks on the Foundations of Mathematics (German/English translation). The Macmillan Company, 1956 (Box 182, Item 69)
    - Wright, G.H. von and Anscombe, G.E.M. Notebooks 1914-1916 by Ludwig Wittgenstein. Harper & Brothers, Basil Blackwell, 1961 (Box 182, Item 70)
    - Anthropologie, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.8. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1922 (Box 182, Item 71)
    - Briefe I, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.9. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1922 (Box 182, Item 72)
    - Briefe II, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.10. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1921 (Box 182, Item 73)
    - Leben und Lehre. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1921 (Box 182, Item 74)
    - Abbott, Thomas Kingsmill. Kant's Critique of Practical Reason and Other Works on the Theory of Ethics. Longmans, Green, and Co. Ltd., 1927 (Box 182, Item 75)
    - Austin, J.L. Sense and Sensibilia. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1962 (Box 182, Item 76)
    - Berkeley, George, Bishop. Theory of Vision and Other Writings. J.M. Dent & Sons Ltd., 1910 (Box 182, Item 77)
    - Bird, Graham. Kant's Theory of Knowledge, An Outline of One Central Argument in the Critique of Pure Reason. The Humanities Press Inc., 1962 (Box 182, Item 78)
    - Bochenski, I.M. et al. The Problem of Universals. University of Notre Dame Press, 1956 (Box 182, Item 79)
    - Crawford, Donald W. Kant's Aesthetic Theory. The University of Wisconsin Press, 1974 (Box 182, Item 80)
    - Kant, Immanuel. Traume eines Geistersehers. Weltgeist-Bucher Verlags-Gesellschaft M.B.H. (Box 182, Item 81)
    - Lachieze-Rey, Pierre. L'Idealisme Kantien. Librairie Felix Alcan, 1931 (Box 182, Item 82)
    - Mahaffy, J.P. and J.H. Bernard. Kant's Critical Philosophy for English Readers. Macmillan and Co., Limited, 1915 (Box 182, Item 83)
    - Paton, H.J. The Categorical Imperative, A Study in Kant's Moral Philosophy. Hutchinson's University Library. (Box 182, Item 84)
    - Prichard, H.A. Kant's Theory of Knowledge. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1909 (Box 182, Item 85)
    - Stevenson, Charles L. Ethics and Language. Yale University Press, 1944 (Box 182, Item 86)
    - Vorkritische Schriften, Band I, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.1. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1912 (Box 182, Item 87)
    - Vorkritische Schriften, Band II, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.2. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1912 (Box 182, Item 88)
    - Kritik Der Reinen Vernunft, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.3. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1913 (Box 182, Item 89)
    - Schriften von 1783-1788, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.4. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1913 (Box 182, Item 90)
    - Kritik Der Praktischen Vernunft, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.5. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1914 (Box 182, Item 91)
    - Schriften von 1790-1796, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.6. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1914 (Box 182, Item 92)
    - Die Metaphysik Der Sitten, Immanuel Kants Werke, v.7. Verlegt Bei Bruno Cassirer, 1916 (Box 182, Item 93)
    - Austin, J.L. How To Do Things With Words. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1962 (Box 182, Item 94)
    - Carnap, Rudolf. Der Logische Aufbau Der Welt. Weltkreis-Verlag, 1928 (Box 182, Item 95)
    - Dodds, E.R. Plato: Gorgias, A Revised Text with Introduction and Commentary. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1959 (Box 182, Item 96)
    - Edwards, Paul and Arthur Pap. A Modern Introduction to Philosophy. The Free Press. (Box 182, Item 97)
    - Hare, R.M. The Language of Morals. Oxford at the Clarendon Press, Oxford University Press, 1952 (Box 182, Item 98)
    - Harvard University. Examinations in Philosophy and Psychology. Harvard University, 1931 (Box 182, Item 99)
    - Klubertanz, George P. The Philosophy of Human Nature. Appleton-Century-Crofts, Inc., 1953 (Box 182, Item 100)